Why are you guys getting so personal with me
?  I mean, you look at my makeup, look at my dress
, look at my jewellery.  But what are you guys
commenting on?  Sister, are these the only heels you have
?  Don't you have any other
heels?  I took it brother, I took the heels.
Now you guys are opening up by burning my bank
account.  First of all I have bought
these trending heels.  And look at its color,
brown color.  You know
how much I like brown color.  And there
is a mix of beige in it too.  Both colors
are my favorites.  And it also has this little bow.
And this looks very cool
brother.  Meaning, wear it in the office, wear it in a party
, wear it anywhere, it looks like a great classy
heel and is also very comfortable after wearing it.
But if you guys had
not made these comments, I would
not have blown the fans into them at all.  Now look, I have
all the red, blue and yellow heels.
But there is nothing to wear under Indian wear.
So I ordered golden
colored heels which look very cute.
Then again, if a person spends money on it, he will definitely
find the thing lovely.  And I felt
it would be a little uncomfortable
because of this transparent strap.  But it is
not uncomfortable at all.  Rest, only
if I go to a wedding, I will be
able to tell what condition my feet are in
after wearing these.  If you
want the link of these heels then comment the
link.  I will send you the link right now.